[{
    "theme": "¿Con o sin ropa?",
    "langread": "es",
    "questions": [{
            "question": "German",
            "answers": ["alemán"]
        },
        {
            "question": "street",
            "answers": ["calle"]
        },
        {
            "question": "lake",
            "answers": ["lago"]
        },
        {
            "question": "substitute",
            "answers": ["sustituto"]
        },
        {
            "question": "strange",
            "answers": ["extraño"]
        },
        {
            "question": "dangerous",
            "answers": ["peligroso"]
        },
        {
            "question": "unique",
            "answers": ["único"]
        },
        {
            "question": "I love it",
            "answers": ["me encanta"]
        },
        {
            "question": "body",
            "answers": ["cuerpo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "naked",
            "answers": ["desnudo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "beautiful",
            "answers": ["hermoso"]
        },
        {
            "question": "sauna",
            "answers": ["sauna"]
        },
        {
            "question": "curious",
            "answers": ["curioso"]
        },
        {
            "question": "laughter",
            "answers": ["risas"]
        },
        {
            "question": "naked",
            "answers": ["encuerado"]
        }
    ]
}]
